Copyright 2007 Sun Microsystems, Inc. All rights reserved.

Sun Microsystems, Inc. has intellectual property rights relating to technology
embodied in the product that is described in this document. In particular, and
without limitation, these intellectual property rights may include one or more
of the U.S. patents listed at http://www.sun.com/patents and one or more
additional patents or pending patent applications in the U.S. and in other
countries.
U.S. Government Rights - Commercial software. Government users are subject to
the Sun Microsystems, Inc. standard license agreement and applicable provisions
of the FAR and its supplements.

Use is subject to license terms.

This distribution may include materials developed by third parties.Sun, Sun
Microsystems, phoneME and Java are trademarks or registered trademarks of Sun
Microsystems, Inc. in the U.S. and other countries.


Copyright 2007 Sun Microsystems, Inc. Tous droits réservés.

Sun Microsystems, Inc. détient les droits de propriété intellectuels relatifs à
la technologie incorporée dans le produit qui est décrit dans ce document. En
particulier, et ce sans limitation, ces droits de propriété intellectuelle
peuvent inclure un ou plus des brevets américains listés à l'adresse
http://www.sun.com/patents et un ou les brevets supplémentaires ou les
applications de brevet en attente aux Etats - Unis et dans les autres pays.

L'utilisation est soumise aux termes du contrat de licence.

Cette distribution peut comprendre des composants développés par des tierces
parties.

Sun, Sun Microsystems, phoneME et Java sont des marques de fabrique ou des
marques déposées de Sun Microsystems, Inc. aux Etats-Unis et dans d'autres pays.



This directory contains a project for the ACL data encoder.

This utility is intended to help to tranclate ACL data from text format to 
ANSI 1.0 DER encoded format.

Format of the input text file is described in the HowToUseACL.txt file.
Input file "acl_0" should be placed in the current directory.

Output files, containig DER encoded information will be generated in the "output" 
directory.
The "output" directory will contain the Data.java file that could be used for the 
acl applet generation and files of the file system that could be downloaded into 
a card file system.

To adjust the utility for your environment it is necessary to correct the 
"build.sh" file.






